Rina Ofuku

Web Developer

ninaofk.com

rs.ivy04@gmail.com

I am a Web developer with 4 years of experience as a Web designer and 2.5 years as a Web Engineer including abundant technical expertise.

I am passionate about listening to clients face-to-face to find out their true needs and create proposals, design and systems for them.

I take pleasure in ensuring customer and user satisfaction by solving their problems and by giving them value through utilization of Web.

Experience

Aden.Corp,Inc.

Web Engineer | Apr 2021 - Aug 2023

- Responsible for developing new functions as the only engineer in the web design department of Osaka branch. Made estimates upon client's request, built and improved features with using PHP(CakePHP) and MySQL.
- Conducted CakePHP workshops that contributed to the grow in value of design team's suggestions by have knowledge about how we create features.

Aden.Corp,Inc.

Web Designer | Apr 2017 - Mar 2021

- Conducted meeting with clients to discuss their needs and suggesting proposals suitable for them, drawing from my wealth of experience.
- Created high-quality wire frames and comprehensible sitemaps to effectively communicate, and designed attractive websites.
- Gained abundant experience creating and building websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP.
- As a project manager, converted, redesigned and added functions legacy sites include 100+ pages to responsive design. Carried out without delay by thorough schedule and resource management.
- · Led and mentored newcomers.
- Created banners of various tastes and designs suitable for the season and purpose.

D.Flat Inc.

Part-time Web Designer | Apr - Sep 2016

- · Created UI parts such as icons for websites and applications.
- · Built foundational knowledge and expertise in creative industries.

Education

Osaka University Of Art Bachelor Of Arts

Department Of Information Design | Apr 2013 - Mar 2017

Skills

Project skills

- · Wire framing
- Prototyping
- Banner, LP, Brand-site, Business-site and Supermarket-site design
- UX/UI design
- · Back-end development
- · Project management
- · Project direction
- · Progress management
- · Data analyzing
- SEO

Tools

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- · Adobe XD
- Figma
- Git
- Docker
- · Google Analytics

Coding and Programming

- · HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Sass
- jQuery
- · PHP CakePHP
- · SQL MySQL
- React Next.js
- · CSS in JS
- Typescript

Languages

- · Japanese Native
- English Upper-Intermediate (CEFR B2)